* In the not too distant future
* Next Sunday A.D.
* There was a guy named Joel
* Not too different
from you or me
* He worked at
Gizmonic Institute
* Just another face
in a red jump suit
* He did a good job
cleaning up the place
* But his bosses didn't like him
* So they shot him into space
* We'll send him cheesy movies
* The worst we can find
* La la la
* He'll have to sit
and watch them all
* Then we'll monitor his mind
* La la la
* Now keep in mind
Joel can't control
* Where the movies begin or end
* Because he used
those special parts
* To make his robot friends
* Robot roll call
* Cambot
* Gypsy
* Tom Servo
* Crow
* If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
* And other science facts
* La la la
* Then repeat to
yourself it's just a show
* I should really just relax
* For Mystery
Science Theater 3000
- Hey everybody,
it's present time.
(cheering)
Okay, all right, that's good.
Hi everybody, welcome to
the satellite of love.
I'm Joel Robinson, and I
decided to give my bots
a little pick me up today.
- What'd I get, what'd I get,
what'd I get, huh, huh, huh?
- Nah, Gypsy, you
didn't get anything.
He forgot he had a
robot named Gypsy.
- Knock it off, you clown.
You want to ruin present
time for being naughty?
- Yeah, Tom Servo.
Hey, Gypsy girl,
look what I got you.
The Little Mermaid
Ariel bath time set.
- Under the sea, under
the sea, under the sea!
- Yeah, good job, yeah.
- Me next, me next, me next.
- [Both] Me, me, me,
me, me, me, me, me.
- Cut it out you
guys, just be cool.
- [Computer] Sign in 15 seconds.
Do Servo's next.
- Alright, Servo,
I got you this.
Junior dragster indoor
funny car by Marks.
- Unbe-cool-lievable!
- Yeah, it goes up
to 30 miles an hour,
and if you run into a wall,
it spins around and heads
the other direction.
- Wow, and it's got a tape deck.
- Yeah, I didn't
know what you liked,
so I threw a few tapes in there.
- Oh, I see
Springsteen, Headies.
These are great, thanks Joel!
- Okay, okay, okay, what'd
you get me, huh, huh?
Come on, come on,
let me have it!
- I saved the best
for last, Crow.
I decided to give you some
dress slacks from JC Penney.
- Oh.
- Oh yeah, come on, you'll
get a lot of use out of them.
You can use them for
dressy or casual,
and well, I'm going
to have to get you
a nice top too, maybe a
pullover or something.
You know, your
birthday is coming up.
Maybe I can give you some
corrective shoes that match.
- Thank you for the pants.
(engine sputtering)
- Yeah, yeah.
Boy, Crow, I sure
wouldn't feel bad,
wait a minute, ease
down, Thundercloud.
There we go, sorry.
You know, I sure wouldn't
feel bad if I were you, Crow.
Wish I could have
gotten those pants.
Yup, least you can get
some use out of 'em.
You know, school, job
interviews, interventions.
Yeah, you're one
lucky dog, Crow.
Well, gotta go, bye!
(engine revving)
- Oh hey Joel, the mad
scientists are calling.
- Oh, I'll get it.
- This is our invention, Joel.
Dr. Clayton Forester
and TV's Frank
will now fulfill our destiny.
The teasing jibes of classmates,
the book dumping
after typing class,
the shameful expulsion
from Chess Club.
These are our only--
- Don't forget all the power
sit-ups they made you do.
- Yes, exactly,
they will bow down--
- The revulsion,
scorn, and rejection
of all the pretty girls.
- Yes, exactly, they shall pay.
- Sophomore year and the
shameful shower incident.
- Yes, thank you Frank.
The point is that we shall
cleave in two this puny planet.
We will crack the Earth as
though it were a china cup,
sending entire
continents plummeting
into the unforgiving sea.
Prepare yourself.
- Hey, may I ask
a stupid question?
Why are you guys doing this?
- Yeah, what do
you get out of it?
- Well, you know, it's kind
of a weird sort of a...
Omega Man kind of thing?
- No, no, it's more of a...
Why don't you go on with
your invention, Joel?
- Well sirs, my invention today
Jim Henson's Edgar
Winter Babies.
- Well, I could see that.
You know, I mean,
they're little dolls,
and there's no pigmentation.
- Oh, why don't we just call
this one a draw, Robinson?
Your movie for today's
experiment makes even me sick,
and I like Morgan
Stewart's Coming Home.
It's called Killer
Shrews, and it stars
James Best from Dukes
of Hazzard fame,
so Frank here is real excited.
- Hey, it was my favorite
show, what can I say?
Oh, by the way, Joel,
before the movie
there's a short,
it's sort of a weird cowboy
thing with horses and kids and.
- [Both] Aww!
(singing)
(alarm buzzing)
- [Tom Servo] Gonna
have fun, huh?
- [Narrator] Junior
Rodeo Daredevils.
- [Joel] Smothered in
gravy, Texas style.
- [Narrator] And it
never would have happened
without that old
timer, Billy Slater.
- [Narrator] Yeah, he's
doing a nickel up at Attica.
- [Narrator] It all
began with a tin can.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah,
doesn't it always.
- [Joel] It's the Gom Jabbar.
- [Narrator] And my
nephew Mike on the right.
- Jim Henson's Misfit Babies.
- [Narrator] Bobby's
taking the low road
and Mike's taking the high road.
- And I'll get to
Scotland before you.
- [Narrator] Quite sure that
Billy Slater won't notice them.
- [Tom Servo] He's hammered.
- [Narrator] And is he
ever going to be surprised
when his old nag starts
running away from her own tail.
But this old
timer's been around.
- [Tom Servo] Why, those little.
- [Narrator] You've
really got to
know your stuff to fool him.
- Get the shotgun,
that'll learn 'em.
- [Tom Servo] Cheese
it, it's the heat!
Looks like the
kid's in the stall.
- I'm gonna teach you
the meaning of law.
- [Joel] Come on,
Quaker Oats for you,
it's the right thing to do.
- [Tom Servo] Both you
pixies got through the barn
and to the hay loft.
- [Narrator] Sheriff Billy
Slater has a hanging tree
all ready for horse rustlers.
- Hey kids, you ever
read the Ox-Bow Incident?
- [Tom Servo] Tough.
- [Narrator] You know
he told Bobby and Mike.
- If I like the crow,
who cares what I like?
- [Narrator] Many
an hombre got hanged
for fooling with horses.
But I've got another
plan for you.
- [Tom Servo] I'm gonna
bury you up to your necks.
- [Narrator] So you think you
know your way around horses?
- [Joel] Sissy Spacek?
- [Narrator] Here's
what you're going to do.
Organize a junior rodeo.
- [Tom Servo] We're doomed.
- [Narrator] Say,
that's an idea.
- [Tom Servo] Not a
good one, but an idea.
- [Joel] What we've got
here are three ideas
our graphic guys came up with.
I hope you like 'em.
- Jim Henson's Last
Picture Show Babies.
- [Joel] Good one.
- [Narrator] Well
sir, let me tell you,
our little cow town never
had seen such goings on.
Billy's youngster
hit us with posters
most everywhere we went.
- [Tom Servo] Then
they started hitting us
with baseball bats.
- [Narrator] Pretty soon,
we were just as head up
about the junior rodeo as
Billy and the kids themselves.
- [Tom Servo] You call that art?
- [Narrator] The whole town
started getting the rodeo bug.
- [Tom Servo] Yee who.
- [Narrator] That went
for some of the best
riders from the high school.
- Hey, Mustang Sally.
- [Narrator] Yeah,
old timer Billy Slater
was really doing a
job with those kids.
- Ah, rodeo's
wasted on the young.
- You know, I see something
subliminal in this here poster.
- [Narrator] Seems like
most everybody in town's
turned out for the great day.
- [Joel] All nine of 'em.
- [Narrator] There's
Hank Evans' Angus bulls
all slicked up for the rodeo.
- [Tom Servo] Everybody
digs Hank Evans.
- And when you come
right down to it,
this whole rodeo's
just another excuse
to crawl inside
a whiskey bottle.
- [Joel] Crow.
- [Narrator] There'll be some
tough competition here today.
Calves for riding and roping.
Into the corral with 'em.
- Animals are to be
bled and slaughtered!
- [Joel] Hey Billy, I'll buy
that Rolling Rock from ya.
- [Tom Servo] No way, beat it.
- [Narrator] Everybody
line up for the first race.
- You're sloppy, you
call that a line?
- [Narrator] Really helping
the kids run their show.
- [Tom Servo] Ah,
a cafe society.
- [Joel] And eat your oatmeal.
- [Narrator] They're off!
- [Joel] I can't stop on my own,
oh how I work, goodbye folks!
- [Tom Servo] I
think maybe rodeos
are the opiate of the masses.
Look at these people.
- [Narrator] Chuck Storm wins.
That was a close finish.
- [Joel] And the Tom
Servod goes wild.
- [All] Yay.
- [Narrator] And there
they go for the lead race.
- Seems like being a
cowboy would kind of suck.
- [Narrator] Get off those
horses fast, grab the bridle.
- Come on, move it,
move it, move it!
- [Joel] Suddenly the
game took a cruel turn.
- [Narrator] Show 'em, cowgirl.
- [Tom Servo] In the sand.
- [Joel] And the
crowd goes wild.
- [All] Yay.
- [Narrator] Calf roping time.
- Big, bold, and brassy.
- [Narrator] And
there goes Mike.
- [Joel] Now, is that
really an efficient way
to bring food to market?
- [Tom Servo] I don't think so.
- [Narrator] Too bad.
Better luck next time, kid.
- Loser.
- [Narrator] Sam Wood, champion
calf roper of junior high.
- You know, the ironic
thing is Sam's a vegetarian,
but there's nothing exciting
about roping okra patty.
- [Narrator] Put
him down, fella.
- You were adopted.
- Now it's the calf
truss up competition.
- [Narrator] 26 seconds.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah, I'm
hot, that's me pretty much.
- [Joel] We'll never
escape this town.
- [Narrator] Jim Rand, champion
calf roper of senior high.
- And next year's janitor.
- [Narrator] Off his
horse in a flash,
just like his dad
in a big-time rodeo.
- [Tom Servo] Holding up the
legacy of secrets and shame.
- You know, some
scars don't heal.
Up next is another young feller.
- [Narrator] 16 seconds.
- [Joel] And the
crowd goes wild.
- [All] Yay.
- [Narrator] Calf
riders, stand by.
- [Joel] I don't really
know what I'm doing!
Oh!
- Why can't Johnny ride?
- [Narrator] Here comes Bobby,
and there he goes.
- [Joel] Fortunately, Bobby
didn't need his spine.
- [Narrator] The girls
aren't bashful, either.
- Like my friend Geeky,
that which does not kill you
makes you stronger.
- [Tom Servo] Oh,
here comes this guy.
- [Narrator] And there
goes the youngest
bull rider of them all.
- [Tom Servo] Ow, dat der
drat it, aw gee criminy.
- [Joel] Go ahead, strip me
of my dignity at age four.
What are you looking at!
- [Narrator] Kind of
tall for a calf rider.
- Not any more.
- [Narrator] Bettie's
in high school.
- [Joel] Used to be.
- [Narrator] You
should see the boys
when she goes square dancing.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah, they
buck her off right away.
- Oh, she can't take a dare.
- [Joel] Anybody get
a license number?
- [Narrator] It's all
the same for Mary Lou,
beauty contest or calf riding.
- [Tom Servo] Uh,
oatmeal's done.
- [Narrator] She
can win 'em both.
Yes sir.
- Yes, yes.
- [Joel] Hey honey, want to
come to my pen for drinks later?
And the crowd goes wild.
- [All] Yay.
- [Narrator] Senior
high bull riding.
- [Tom Servo] Fresh
off the grill.
- [Narrator] This Angus
bull is no hobby horse.
- No, it's garbage.
- [Tom Servo] He's
a moveable feast.
- [Narrator] Will you look
at that bull, he's really--
- [Tom Servo] Oh, take
the rope off my groin.
- [Joel] Here comes the
last surviving castrati.
- [Narrator] Only two years
ago he was still riding calves.
- Now he sells pencil and
string on street corners.
- [Narrator] Dad's going to
be mighty proud of him today.
- If he can find him.
Oh no, oh no, this is wrong.
I signed up for debate!
- [Narrator] Just six seconds.
- [Tom Servo] Over Tokyo.
- [Narrator] And here's
Slash Barcay's meanest bronc.
- That horse has
got Air Jordan's on.
- [Narrator] Sits him like
he was glued to the saddle.
- I am!
- [Tom Servo] Hey, hey,
you're crowding my lane.
- [Joel] And the
crowd goes wild.
- [All] Yay.
- [Narrator] Okay
Glen, get out there
and show them how to do it.
- [Joel] Or don't
come home tonight.
- I am not an animal.
- [Narrator] Watch out,
that ground's awful hard.
- [Joel] Life is awful hard.
- [Narrator] We sure
had us a junior rodeo.
- Next week, geriatric rodeo.
- [Narrator] And then it
came prize giving time.
- [Tom Servo] First
price, bronze cow chips.
- [Narrator] Prizes for winning.
- Even George F.
Kaufman won a prize.
- [Narrator] And
prizes for trying.
- [Joel] In other
words, bitter failure.
- It's Hayley Mills.
- Sure loved you
in The Parent Trap.
- [Narrator] Yes sirree, the
junior rodeo is here to stay,
and nobody's happier about it
than old-timer Billy Slater.
- [Tom Servo] It's sad, really.
* And the guys are
not clowning all day
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Those
who hunt by night
will tell you that the
wildest and most vicious
of all animals--
- [Tom Servo] Are in Vegas?
- [Narrator] Is the tiny shrew.
- [All] A shrew?
- [Narrator] Feeds only
by the dark of the moon.
- Yeah, just go with
us on this, okay?
- [Narrator] He must
eat his own body weight
every few hours.
- [Tom Servo] Plus
a delicious shake.
- [Narrator] And the
shrew devours everything,
bones, flesh,
marrow, everything.
- He can really
tuck away a moth.
- [Narrator] First in
Alaska, and then invading
steadily southward, there
were reports of a new species.
- [Joel] A fun species.
- [Narrator] The
giant killer shrew.
- So there!
- The.
- Killer.
- Shrews.
- Starring Joan Collins
and Jackie Collins.
- [Joel] Oh, Ingrid is
good, but James is best.
- [Tom Servo] I think so.
- [Joel] Based on a
novel by William Shatner.
Spock.
- Oh, the great
William M. Cline.
Wilfred (chuckles).
- [Tom Servo] Oh, I passed
a blue stone last night,
let me tell you.
- [Joel] No shrews were hurt
during the making
of this picture.
- [Tom Servo] Well, a few, but.
Big Ben Chapman.
- Matthew, if you ain't
the orneriest sprout
that ever jumped on my lawn.
- [Joel] Hey, Ray Kellogg,
he directed The
Giant Gila Monster.
- [Tom Servo] No, no!
Oh, it's Robert Maxwell's boat.
Mr. Maxwell, Mr. Maxwell.
- [Joel] Hey, it's PT
90210, check it out.
- Sure is a lot of
quiet out there.
- Too lot of quiet.
- Almost smell it, can't you?
- [Joel] No, that's me.
- No, but I can feel it.
The pressure's dropped so fast,
it's almost made my ears pop.
- [Joel] Chew gum.
- Hurricane's got definite
ways of telling you it's there.
Where is it?
- I thought you knew.
- Dead ahead.
- [Joel] Do you think I'm heavy?
- What's that mean to us.
- Now boy, that puts our port
right in the middle of it.
- Oh God help me.
- There's a cove on
the lee side, though.
We'll snuggle up close to
the bluff and ride it out.
- We most certainly will not.
- Well, the chart shows it's
good holding ground, it's clay.
- [Joel] Yep.
- You know something?
- [Joel] What?
- If this thing had
an automatic pilot,
I wouldn't have to
put up with you.
- Then you wouldn't
have nobody to chew out.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah, wait til
the whip comes down, white boy.
- Be there in a couple of hours,
these mills of
yours keep running.
- Look, automatic pilots
can't play dixieland jazz
on their banjos like I can.
- (laughs) Good point.
- What the heck did that mean?
- [Joel] They're trolling
kind of fast, aren't they?
- [Tom Servo] They're
gonna lose bait.
- Hey, Rook.
Rook, come here.
- These things make
everything look bigger!
- Take a look.
There she is, dead ahead.
- Oh yeah, it's Gilligan's
Island, the headhunter episode.
- Man, that sure do look good.
- [Joel] Mrs. Howell?
- Man named Craigis owns
the island, does he?
- That's the name on the
crate, Dr. Milo Craigis.
- We'll unload tomorrow.
I don't want this craft
sitting high in the water
when that blow hits.
- [Tom Servo] Yes, yes.
- With a lot of water under?
- That's right.
That sea won't pick
up in that cove,
that wind'll have it
whipping around like a kite.
Step forward and break out
the heavy weather hook.
Check and make sure
it's free to run.
- Yeah, but a heavy weather
hook can't play dixieland jazz.
- Alright, Joel, alright.
- Hey, say, like
Robinson Crusoe,
this is as primitive as can be.
- Bet Robinson Crusoe
can't play dixieland jazz.
- Would you knock it off
about dixieland jazz?
- Oh, I know this, this is
the famous dock walking scene.
You know, this whole take
was done in one shot.
It's a planned sequence, like
the opening of Touch of Evil
and the Copa Cabana
scene in Goodfellows.
This is virtuoso
filmmaking, fellas,
you got to see it to believe it.
Now Brian De Palma
used this in um,
in, in Bonfire of the Vanities,
really exciting,
it's splendiferous.
- Well, we've covered
the waterfront.
- Ah, she'll ride like a duck.
If she swings too
far to starboard,
we might have to take
a check line to shore.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah, whatever.
- Hey, Rook, take a
slant up that trail.
- Hey, this island's
got oak trees!
- Now that's a rather strange
set up, wouldn't you say?
- Yeah, but the
punchline makes it work.
- Looks like somebody's
getting rid of somebody.
- [Joel] Sometime.
- Maybe.
Hard to tell.
- But I bet they can't
play dixieland jazz--
- [Tom Servo] Shut up.
- Like Columbus, we claim
this island for, oh, hi.
- [Joel] Uh, I'm the
temp you ordered.
- I'm Dr. Craigis.
- Yeah, right, whatever,
who's the lady?
- Got your supplies aboard.
- That's good.
Nothing wrong with
Captain Peterson, I hope.
- Well, I wouldn't know.
- Ever heard of Slim Fast?
- I just bought his run.
- Oh, I see.
Were you able to fill my order?
- Everything on the list.
Here's the manifest.
- [Tom Servo] Destiny.
- Missing last week's supply
has run us a little short.
Captain, after you've unloaded,
I have a passenger for you.
Ann.
Captain Sherman, this is
my daughter Ann Craigis.
- So hands off.
- Well, so you're the passenger.
- That's right, captain.
- Well, it's going to be
nice having you aboard.
I'm getting a little tired
of looking at Griswald.
- [Joel] Can you
play dixieland jazz?
- We're not leaving today.
- [Joel] Oh, well, I--
- [Tom Servo] Huh?
Huh?
Oh?
- In fact, we're
not even unloading.
- In fact, we don't even exist.
- That load will cut
the roll in half.
- Now wait, you don't
have a line yet.
- Yes, animals.
- Game or otherwise.
- Under certain conditions,
it could be dangerous.
- [Joel] He's right, you know.
- Hey Rook, you want
to shake the kinks out,
limber up a little.
- Not me, captain,
but you go right ahead
and stretch your legs.
That ship's going
to be bucking like
a bucking bronco before long.
'Sides, I got some
work left to do.
- A simple yes or no will do.
- If you come
ashore, wear a gun.
- Got you, captain.
- [Tom Servo] And if
you go to San Francisco,
wear some flowers in your hair.
- [Joel] Gotcha, captain.
Oh, he must be scouting
locations for Dukes of Hazzard.
- Ooh.
Boss Hogg'll love this place.
- [Tom Servo] I'd say
they went a bit overboard
on the fence.
- [Joel] No sense
of perspective.
- [Tom Servo] You know, they
should have put a gate in it,
for crying out loud.
- [Joel] I've fallen in with a
group of ham radio operators.
- When I told you
about the hurricane,
you acted like you didn't
know anything about it.
- Hurricane Carter?
- What's the matter,
your set broken down?
- We've been out
of communication
for more than a week, captain.
- Can it be fixed?
- Totally out of commission.
- What he said.
- My assistant.
Mr. Farrell, Jerry Farrell.
- Jerry Farrell?
Hey, did he go to Haroldson
Elementary School?
- [Joel] Hey, Freddy Fender.
- Father, perhaps the
captain will enjoy a drink.
- Well, of course.
Will you join us in a cocktail?
- Well, I've never been known
to turn down a drink yet.
I'll be glad to accept.
- I've been known to beg for
them, as a matter of fact.
- In that case
we'll have martinis.
Mario.
- Si, senor.
- Mix them, please.
- Mix 'em please,
what's he talking about?
- [Joel] What a scene.
- Right this way, captain.
- You know those
little cocktail napkins
with the jokes on them?
I love those little guys.
- [Tom Servo] Uh, check your
gun at the door, Festus.
- [Joel] There, bad door.
Okay, don't say hi, ga.
- Sounds like Flash Gordon.
- [Tom Servo] What a dump.
Who said that, George?
- You have everything
here you need?
- We are self-sufficient here.
We have cows for fresh milk,
chickens for fresh eggs.
- [Tom Servo] Gin, rum,
pickled eggs, mixers.
- Sort of a world all your own.
- That's exactly what
I've tried to create.
- Well, to each his own.
If you have to be
isolated for your work,
you've picked a
lonely little island.
- What are you getting
at, what's your point?
- Excuse me, please,
I think I'll change.
- Why'd you go and
say that to her?
Geez, let's leave.
(doors closing)
- Tom, I knew that
shirt was going to
push some bad buttons for
Joel and get him started
doing that Will Rogers thing
he's been talking about.
- And you were right, Crow.
By the way, I do love
those pants (laughs).
- Oh, I ought to pants you.
- Shh, here he comes.
- Well, howdy folks,
how you doing?
You know, I've been
listening to what
the President's
been doing, and it
kind of seems to
me like he's trying
to crawl into the wrong end
of the cracker barrel, hyuck.
- Moo.
- Uh, bristle, I guess.
- Yeah, I'm a lot
like you folks.
I'm simple, you know,
and I been hearing
the President go on and on,
and it kind of seems to me
like the polecat's
got caught in the cow
and it's time for the hound dog
to skitter him out of there.
(Tom Servo moos)
- Hey, this is fun.
(moos)
- Pretty good at it, too.
Bristle, bristle.
- Oh yeah, you know,
kind of reminds me
of Aunt Martha's
mustache, you know.
Makes a fella hungry for some
down home dogfish, don't it.
- What?
- The rumors of my death have
been greatly exaggerated.
- That's not Will Rogers.
(moos)
- Yup, it's not
over til it's over.
- And that's Casey Stengel.
What's he doing?
- I don't know,
it's crazy there.
- Yup, yup, yup.
Oh, well everything
I love is either
illegal, immoral, or fattening.
Take a bite out of crime.
- Wait a minute, Alexander
Walcott and McGruff?
He's all over the map.
Joel, you okay?
Come here, buddy (whistles).
- Yup, we will bury you.
- Khrushchev?
Oh, Joel.
- Yup, baseball been
berry, berry good to me.
- Oh, now he's doing
Garrett Morris.
- Really sad.
- Just toying with us.
Let's get out of here.
- Anybody here seen
my old friend John?
- Ah, ah, Joel, let me go!
I want to go iron my pants!
- Yup, yup, yup, it's
morning in America.
- No, it is not.
- Yup.
One fish, two fish,
red fish, blue fish.
(light music)
- Hey, I thought, you're
gonna hurt somebody with this.
- [Tom Servo] Well,
it was your idea.
- I can understand that.
- [Joel] Ouch!
- Sorry.
- [Joel] How would you know?
- Hey.
Bob Clampett.
- [Tom Servo] So how's your
novel coming along there?
- Radford.
- [Joel] Rapid?
Bathroom?
- Radford, would you
please step over here.
- [Joel] Rapid, bathroom?
- Just a second, doc.
- [Joel] Yes, this is
our resident novelist,
Rapid Bathroom.
- Doctor Baines.
- There's no need to shout,
doctor, I'm right here.
- I'd like you to meet
Captain Thorne Sherman.
- [Joel] Stone Shrimp?
- How do you do?
- Two new litters
since lunch, doctor.
Both support GT-116.
- That's good, but uh--
- We can breed them to the 205
group in about three weeks.
But I'd prefer to
wait and expose
about half of them to the--
- [Joel] Hey, relax.
- If you agree.
- Good idea.
Do you know there's
a hurricane coming?
- No, but if you hum a few bars.
- Well I don't
suppose there's much
we can do about that.
Glad to meet you.
- [Joel] Could you get me a
few Denver Pyle autographs?
- [Tom Servo] We need
the eggs, as they say.
- You have to excuse Radford.
- [Joel] He smells.
- Anything that does
not concern his project
does not get through to him.
Brilliant mind.
He would starve to death
if someone didn't
remind him to eat.
- Must be very interesting work.
What's his field?
- [Tom Servo] Of dreams.
- Biology.
He specializes in
genetics, heredity.
- I'm afraid my interest doesn't
run in that line, you know.
- Get out.
- If you could
isolate and identify
the inherited
factor in each gene.
- Now wait a minute, I'm afraid
I'm not very good
with pure research.
- This is practical research.
- I'm not good at that, either.
- The theory among mammals,
the smaller the size,
the higher the metabolism
and shorter the lifespan.
- Is that right.
- Well, I'm attempting
to decrease the size
by maintaining a low metabolism
and resultant a longer lifespan.
- What reason?
- You think he'd come up
with a hair growth thing
if he was so smart.
- I'd like to hit
you really hard.
- In time.
- [Joel] Hey, it's Cousin
Marilyn from the Munsters.
- Oh.
- If we were half as
big as we were now,
we could live twice as long
on our natural resources.
- She's got her
apron on backwards.
- Father, may I speak
with you a moment?
Will you please
excuse us, captain?
- Well, providing
you drop the captain.
- [Tom Servo] Ouch.
- I prefer Thorne.
- Dad, this scientist thing is
cute, but it's wearing thin.
- [Joel] Mm hmm,
that's good booze.
- Tell him, tell him now.
- Tell me something, doctor.
- [Joel] Why do
fools fall in love?
- Has a hurricane ever
hit this island before
that you know of?
- I wouldn't know.
We've only been
here nine months,
and this place has been
unoccupied for years.
- Well, have you ever
been through one?
- [Tom Servo] Have
you ever been mellow?
- Only the fringes.
- Well, this one's
building up very fast,
pressure dropped very
quickly in the center.
I'd advise you to get
some doors and windows
open in this place.
- Yes, Mr. Ventilation.
- Ventilators on the roof,
and if you'll freshen Ann's
drink, I'll go and check them.
- Flesh in man's drink?
- [Tom Servo] I don't get it.
- Thank heavens you arrived.
- Frosty malt?
- Why, rations
are getting short?
- No, it's more than
that, much more.
We'll surely be able to
sail tomorrow, won't we?
- Possibly.
But not probable.
Not til late, anyway.
Takes a long time for a sea
like that to quiet down.
- But if you're worried
about me, you needn't.
I'm a good sailor.
- Aye aye, all hands on deck.
- We'll sail when
the time's right.
- [Marlowe] Got them
opened all right.
- [Tom Servo] That's
great, now close them up.
- Well captain, let
me freshen your drink.
- [Tom Servo and Joel]
Flesh in your drink?
- [Joel] That's what he said.
- Not trying to rush you, but--
- Get out, get out!
- I've invited Thorne
for dinner, father.
- [Joel] Does anybody
know the plot yet?
- Oh, I see.
- [Joel] London, I see France.
- If you're not worried about
your ship, you're welcome.
- I'll take a rain
check on that dinner.
- If you wish.
- Father, I've asked
Thorne to stay.
- Hey everybody, what
does this remind you of?
- [Joel] He's a brilliant
man, but he saves his phlegm.
- Sole survivor of group 30.
28 months old today.
* Happy birthday to you
- That's right,
yet still maintains
low metabolism without
any sluggishness.
- [Joel] He's the guy who
taught LBJ how to hold dogs.
- It certainly sets our course.
- Radford, suspend series 52--
- [Joel] Ratford?
- What the heck is
he talking about?
- What is that?
- It's a sorex soricidae.
- [Tom Servo] But
I call him Rick.
- Looks like a small rat.
Smells like a skunk.
- [Joel] Looks delicious.
- These little fellas
are our subjects.
They have a birth
cycle of 10 to 14 days,
and using them we
can establish traits.
- This guy makes Al
Louis look handsome.
- Over a short period of time.
- Well, how big do they get?
(dramatic music)
- How big does that
music make it sound?
- That's an adult.
- I've got a big, dirty secret.
- See, the muzzle is longer
and thicker than the rats.
- [Tom Servo] Thicker?
- It extends over the
lower mandible, see?
- [Joel] Guys, want to
get back to the movie?
- [Tom Servo] Be nice.
- I can't think of my line.
- All he knows is his next meal.
- [Joel] Which is you.
- He's just been fed.
He'll be alright for
another eight hours.
(loud banging)
(Ann screams)
- Honey, switch to decaf.
- A shutter blew open.
Radford.
- I've got it.
- Ow, aw, gee.
- You let that scare you?
- [Tom Servo] Does it bug you?
- Storms have always
frightened her,
ever since she was a child.
(singing tune from
Hawaii Five-O)
They're not climbers.
They are digging animals,
a lot like the mole.
- Let me drop it
down your shirt.
- They feed only at night
unless they're starving.
And when they are hungry enough,
they'll tackle anything,
regardless of size.
- [Joel] Like LT,
Lawrence Taylor.
- Keep two of them in a cage
for 12 hours without food,
the stronger will
eat the weaker.
- It's fun.
- They're cannibals.
- Precisely.
- [Joel] Don't say cannibal.
- Requires a tremendous
amount of energy.
To supply it, they
must eat three times
their own weight in food
every 24 hours, or starve.
- Guys, guys, that was
covered in the voiceover
at the beginning of the movie.
- [Joel] Alright, I want you
to pick a card, any card,
out of the middle of
the deck is fine now.
- Some call them bone eaters.
- I call them cheddarwurst.
- When the flesh is
gone, they'll eat
the bones for marrow.
All they'll leave are
teeth, horns, hooves--
- I could use another
martini, do you mind?
- Of course, my dear.
I'll get you one.
- You don't pick
your family, do you?
- Just humor him,
he's not well, hi.
- There you are.
- [Tom Servo] Drink it down.
- Mario.
Mario!
- Yes, Mr. Beatty.
- Mario will show
you to the bath,
you will freshen up a bit.
(speaking in foreign language)
- Hit him with the bathroom?
- Oh Nita, what are
you trying to prove?
- [Joel] Finish your drink.
Well, listen, here's
the caveman room.
You'll really enjoy it.
- Turtle Bulkowski
was here before you,
sorry about the mess.
- The martini faucet's in
back, oh, you found it.
- Oh, strip over the toilet,
sanitized for my protection.
- Is your room comfortable, sir?
Can I unpack your hat?
- [Joel] Uh, please don't
drink from the bidet.
- You got a problem, too?
Que paso?
- Nada, nothing, senor.
But you will leave
on the ship tomorrow.
- Well, I think that all depends
on the wind and
the sea, don't you?
- Si.
- [Joel] Regular Walt
Whitman, aren't you?
- I don't know.
Ah, you're joking.
(laughing)
I see it, boy.
I see.
- Well, I'm glad to hear that.
If anybody else is concerned
about my sailing tomorrow
why, you see they feel
the point too, huh?
- Ouch.
- I don't like
repeating myself.
- Okay, Senor.
(upbeat music)
(whooshing)
- [Joel] Oh, he's got to plug
in the boat for the night.
Aw, someone left the
cake out in the rain.
- [Tom Servo] What's
he doing there?
Oh, I get it!
This is Knot's Landing!
- I know, but I'm not saying
that you created them.
I am saying that because
of your drunken stupidity
in leaving the cage door open,
you created the horrible
situation that now exists.
- [Tom Servo] Now, Miss Kitty--
- Like any one of
us might have made.
I'm getting a little
sick of being called
an irresponsible drunk.
(Joel coughing)
Now believe me, I am.
- [Tom Servo] Hi, is
the irresponsible drunk,
oh, there you are!
- Excuse me.
- [Tom Servo] Two people
per scene, please.
- [Joel] All right, I'm leaving,
and as soon as I close the
door, I'm gone, all right?
So, shrew?
- Care for a cigarette?
- [Tom Servo] Why, thank you.
I have emphysema.
- Thank heavens
you arrived today.
- You said that before.
What's the strain?
- [Ann] I don't understand.
- [Tom Servo] Aw, nuts, I got
my shirt caught in the door.
- I want to leave, but I
want my father to go with me.
- Well then, why doesn't he?
- We've discussed it many
times, but he's adamant.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, he's Adam Ant.
I didn't know.
- I'm sure Jerry has a lot
to do with his decision.
- [Tom Servo] Now
who's this Jerry the,
oh, I'm Jerry.
- Had to convince me that
the crisis will only last
for a few--
- Oh, hi.
- [Joel] What?
Oh, you see, I forgot my thing,
and, huh, I need it for
this thing I'm doing.
- This is certainly
a cozy little scene.
- [Tom Servo] It
was gonna be cozy.
- Might even be called intimate.
Boy meets girl--
- Stop it, Jer.
What I do or have to say
does not concern you.
- I can't disagree
with you more, my dear.
I'm concerned with
everything you do
and I intend to
keep it that way.
- [Joel] I'm outta here.
- Now, in my book an engagement
isn't a casual thing.
- In my book it isn't either.
And last night ended ours.
(wind whooshing)
- [Tom Servo] Dorothy, Dorothy!
- Hey, that sounds like
a Dixieland jazz band.
- Now he's doing it.
- Oh, stop it!
(wind whooshing)
- Careful.
Cute little gun.
Puppies!
- Oh, yeah.
(gunshots)
- [Tom Servo] Sit, stay!
Sit, oh, you stay!
You stay, you stay, you stay!
Sit! (smooching)
(thunder rumbling)
- [Tom Servo] Oh, will ya
look at those pants go?
- Kinda feels good, mmm.
(suspenseful music)
- Uh-oh.
- [Tom Servo] Uh-oh, big dog!
Oh, run! (sputtering)
(thunder rumbling)
(suspenseful music)
Hmm.
(Tom Servo babbling)
- Gee, they're just puppies.
What's he running
from puppies for?
- [Joel] Hi there,
I'm Kurt Dowdy.
We're out hunting with George
Kirby from Big Texas Shrew
and it's really not
going that well.
- [Tom Servo] Ren, Stimpy, no!
- Help, help!
Captain Thorne!
Somebody help!
- Go away, go away!
I'll help you.
- [Tom Servo] Hey, just
throw us your wallet.
(thunder rumbling)
Wait 'til I finish my Saratoga.
- Be reasonable.
Everybody in the world is
scared to death of something.
- That's evident.
When they came at us last night,
you knocked me down
getting inside the fence.
- It's just that I
can't stand them.
- Oh, now I've discovered
something I can't stand.
- Spackle.
It bugs me.
- All right.
But I advise you not to
mention it to anyone.
- [Tom Servo] And don't
leave the country.
- I'm gonna complete these
experiments with your father
regardless of anything,
do you understand that?
Nobody is gonna take
this chance away from me.
- [Tom Servo] Your
breath smells like feet!
- Where's Captain Sherman?
- Checking the weather.
I'll get him.
(Joel humming)
(exclaiming)
- [Ann] Captain,
time for dinner.
- [Joel] Man, it's
really breezy in my room.
- [Tom Servo] We're
having tobacco salad
with a light gin dressing.
- Meanwhile, back at the branch.
- [Tom Servo] D'oh!
- Help!
Somebody, help!
- Hang in there, baby.
Friday's coming.
(shrews screeching)
- Ooh.
You know, this is another
one of those scenes
that is so offensive
on so many levels.
- [Tom Servo] I hear ya.
- [Tom Servo] Uh-oh,
he's shooting the ground!
- [Tom Servo] A little
Roscoe for ya, shew!
(Rook screaming)
- D'oh, they're
licking me, stop it!
No, stop it, cut
it out! (laughing)
Oh, it tickles!
- [Tom Servo] They're
licking him to death.
How cute! (laughing)
(shrews screeching)
- I'm shakin' the bush, boss.
(suspenseful music)
(shrews screeching)
- Hmm.
(thunder rumbling)
- [Joel] Ooh, he exploded!
Hmm.
- I hate the smell of wet shrew.
(rumbling)
- [Tom Servo] Are the
dogs and shrews friends?
Is that what's going on?
(Ann gasping)
(explosion)
- [Joel] I think I just
heard Griswald explode.
You?
- A miss is as good as a mile,
I always say.
- You know, if one of those
trees crashes through,
it might just knock the whole--
- Look, honey, any tree
on this side of the house
will fall away from
it, so just relax.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, you're
a tree surgeon now?
- I think I'd better
go back aboard.
Oh, don't think I'm not
grateful for your hospitality.
I am.
- But you're out of liquor so.
- Your ship is safe.
Please, stay here with me.
- [Joel] Is there
somebody under that dress?
- Are you scared or lonesome?
- [Tom Servo] Chicken,
chicken. (bawking)
- I'll take a rain check on it.
- Thorne, you can't leave.
No one opens that
gate after dark.
- Well, who's
gonna stop me, you?
- How about this?
- [Joel] How about
my friend, Roscoe?
- No one opens
that gate at night.
(thunder rumbling)
- [Tom Servo] Open that
gate, come on, Robin!
Open that gate!
- Now, look, I
don't ask questions
because it's against
my principles.
- [Tom Servo] Your what?
- Wouldn't you like
to explain that?
- [Joel] Well, you see,
the hammer hits the primer
and the primer--
- Give me the gun.
Not very becoming anyway.
- Oh, rats.
- You believe in fairy tales?
- [Tom Servo] Does
it got elves in it?
- Well, I'm a little old
for that sort of thing,
but what'd you have in mind?
- Well, I'll tell you about one.
A true fairy tale, and you
arrived in the middle of it.
- Oh?
- [Ann] Have you ever
heard of a shrew?
- As in Taming of the--
- No, the animal.
Radford called them
sorex soricidae when
he showed you one.
- Oh, then shrew must
be the common name
for those cute little animals.
- Cute?
- No, they're adorable.
- That's the last
word you can use
to describe those monsters.
They're the most
horrible animals on
the face of the earth.
- A murderer?
- My father told you,
they breed within three
weeks after birth.
Their lifespan is
around one year.
- Yeah, I know what
your father told me,
but what's that got to do
with me opening that gate?
- Pick another category, please.
Still your turn.
- There are 200 or 300
giant shrews out there.
- [Joel] Not counting
the dogs, right?
- Monsters weighing
between 50 and 100 pounds.
- [Tom Servo] How
did she weigh 'em?
- 50 to 100 pounds?
- Pounds?
- Wait a minute,
you must be kidding.
- I am definitely not kidding.
- [Tom Servo] I'm
not pulling your leg.
- [Thorne] That's as big
as a full-grown wolf.
- And what's more, they
are beginning to starve.
- [Joel] She's got a real
Hawaii 5-0 hairdo there.
- No wonder you didn't
want me to go out there.
Thanks for saving my skin.
- Well, I'm sorry I had to
threaten you with a gun.
But I didn't know
how else to stop you.
- No, it was very effective.
- Quite a turn-on.
- All you had to do
was tell me about--
- What is this,
fill in the blank?
- But you changed everything
when you started to leave,
and I had to stop you some way.
- [Joel] I would've been alone.
I'd rather kill
you than be alone.
- You say there's
200 or 300 out there?
- [Tom Servo] Where'd
they get our address?
- Ann.
- [Tom Servo] Well,
now, Matthew, I sure
could use a gimlet.
- That's right, Captain Thorne.
And if you'd stuck with your
rowboat and played captain
instead of trying
to play detective,
you wouldn't have to worry about
how many are out
there, would you?
- [Dr. Craigis]
That's enough, Jerry.
- That's a pretty complex
insult for a drunk.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
Oh, now it's like an
Agatha Christie novel, hmm?
- [Dr. Craigis]
What's wrong, Ann?
- Mr. Thorne decided to leave.
To dissuade him I started to
tell him about the shrews.
- [Tom Servo] Shoes, what
about, oh, shrews, oh!
- [Dr. Craigis] You might
as well know the whole story
as half of it.
- For story?
- [Joel] Doesn't anybody
think about Griswald?
- [Tom Servo] I've
heard this one before.
- [Dr. Craigis] I guess we're
all a little jumpy, Captain.
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- [Joel] You're about to
light the filter, Captain.
- Six months ago we
managed to isolate
the factor controlling size.
- [Joel] Ah, what
a night that was.
- Two litters were born.
Six individuals kept for study.
- [Joel] A prosthetic?
- They were about the
size of buckshot at birth.
- Hey, he's tall.
- But the rate of growth
was abnormal.
- I'm on the edge of my chair.
- They continued to grow, grow.
- Whoa.
- They were mutants.
- Jailbreak tonight!
Everyone through the wire!
- [Dr. Craigis] Somehow
they managed to escape.
(upbeat music)
- One, two.
- One, two, three, four.
* Killer shrew
* Don't know the diff
between me and you
* It comes on at night
* To give you a fright
* Don't look now but
he's gonna take a bite
* Da da da da
* Da da da da da da-da-da
* Killer shrew
* K-I-Double L-E-R shrew
* He's scary and tall
* If that's not enough
* He's augmented with
bad man and stuff
* Killer shrew
* He's coming to
your town to get you
- Killer shrew, by Marx.
- All right!
That was great!
- Okay, well, consumer Joel.
That's the enticing jingle.
Now play the
super-fun board game!
- Wait a minute, you
guys came up with this
all by yourselves?
- El posivito, senorito.
C'mon, let's play.
You can be the German guy
and I'll pick the card.
Right over there.
- All right, okay, gotcha.
It says, "Contemplate shrews."
- Okay, that means
you don't move.
Okay, now I pick one.
- Okay, I'll do that for you.
Okay.
- Okay, have another martini.
Okey-doke, I'm the girl, so
I'll just move one piece.
Oh, you see, it's glued
down, and you can't move it.
It's just like the
movie, nobody moves!
(Crow and Tom Servo laughing)
In fact, nobody moves at
all for over 45 minutes!
It's enough to numb your brain.
They sit and talk
and nothing happens,
and then, cripes, Frank Cannon
gets more action than this.
- Crow--
- You think something
might happen
and your spirit soars,
but all that happens
is the black girl changes
and she's not even that cute!
- Crow--
- And the Cuban guy mumbles
- and so does the Captain
and they all just drink more!
- I'm scared, I'm scared!
(Crow babbling)
- Can't tell what this is!
(Crow and Tom Servo sobbing)
- Aww, that's okay, that's okay.
Joel's got you, it's
all right, it's okay.
No, you guys, you didn't
have to do this for me.
You're both such troopers,
in the theater, quippin'
like there's no tomorrow,
making kooky comments
on contemporary mores.
You know, making
arcane references
at the drop of a hat,
I love you little guys!
- Thanks, Joel.
We love you too.
- It's just, you were
so funny in the theater,
we didn't know if you could
tell this movie was a honk shoe.
- A honk shoe?
What's that?
- Oh, you know, honk
shoe. (imitating snoring)
(all laughing)
(all sighing)
(beeping)
(all exclaiming)
(clicking, whooshing)
- About a month later...
(chattering)
They were multiplying.
We did everything in the
world to exterminate them,
but (scoffing) no apparent luck.
- [Joel] Did you
try Roach Motel?
- We haven't seen any,
since daylight blinds them
and they forage only at
night when they're starving.
- [Tom Servo] Hmm, he's got
a few hairs left up there.
- But the fact that two of
them charged Ann and Jerry
at the gate last
evening indicates
that the available
food on the island
is nearing depletion.
- [Crow] Well, let's
have a food drive!
- Then what, Doctor?
- [Tom Servo] That's
it, don't you get it?
- It will take a couple days.
- What do we do
during that time?
- [Joel] Well,
there's always liquor.
- Stay indoors and
wait until it's over.
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] Oh no!
They've got wire cutters!
- [Thorne] I guess some wires
are down on the transom.
- [Ann] I'm sorry.
- [Joel] Everyone, quick,
light your martinis!
- [Jerry] Mario!
Mario!
- [Mario] Si, senor?
- There's a light
in the pack there.
Light it and bring it in here.
- [Joel] I'll fix the drinks.
- [Jerry] Radford, light all
the candles you can find.
- All right, I will.
- And curse the darkness.
- [Craigis] Outside.
Can't get at it at night.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom Servo] She's kind
of wearing fluffy culottes,
isn't she?
- Mm-hmm.
- A lantern will give you
all the light you need.
- [Joel] It's just as
light with candles.
- [Tom Servo] Hmm, amazing.
- [Tom Servo] This is
like a bad production
of a Chekhov play.
A wild geese.
- I don't like you.
(thunder rumbling)
- Well, Jerry, I
felt she was sincere
and made sense.
- Stop talking
and finish my pedicure.
- Wanting her father
to leave the island
with her makes sense?
It'd be much better
for the project
if I went with her
for a few days.
- [Tom Servo] Maybe
the Fanta suites.
- As a matter of fact,
I think I'll talk to
the doctor about that.
That might be the answer.
- Oh, great, it'll be a
20-minute scene, I'm sure.
- I don't think much
of this Thorne Sherman.
He looks to me like the
type that'd try anything.
- [Joel] Oh, really?
I think he's a really nice guy.
- That left-handed
dinner invitation.
That was just to keep me here
'til after dark, wasn't it?
- [Crow] I'm sorry, I was
sure you were left handed.
Can you eat with either hand?
- I wanted you here tonight.
I felt something terrible
was going to happen.
- Well, you still feel
the same way about it?
- Not as much, not since you're
here and know everything.
- [Joel] I don't
know everything.
I don't even know how fish work.
(suspenseful music)
- Oh, puppy!
Ooh, cute.
- No, not Fury!
- The biggest shrew of all.
- That was weird.
- I love an open
fire, don't you?
- Mm-hmm.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah,
they're great.
- [Joel] And I
love an open sewer.
- The wind has the
lonesomest sound.
Doesn't it?
- [Tom Servo] Wheat,
nothing but miles of wheat.
- Back in Sweden we don't
have a wind this strong.
- [Crow] Tell me
about your home world.
- You're a strange man, Thorne.
- [Joel] You're a queer duck.
- I never met anyone like you.
- [Thorne] Oh?
- You seem so disinterested
in everything.
- [Tom Servo] Uh-huh.
Look, you bore the
heck out of me.
- Aren't you the
least bit curious?
- [Joel] Yellow?
- Don't you wonder about the
unusual things around here?
- [Crow] Do you ever wonder
where felt comes from?
- The guns, the fence?
The shuttered windows?
My accent, anything?
- I'll tell you something.
I'm only interested in
anything that concerns me,
then I do something about it.
(horse neighing)
- [Joel] Did you
say Frau Blooker?
- You're gonna stay
with me tomorrow,
whether your father (horse
whinnying drowns out Thorne).
- [Tom Servo] He was Mister Ed.
- [Ann] Thorne, no!
- [Crow] No, don't
go in the bathroom!
We don't have a fan in there!
- [Ann] Out there!
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom Servo] Kim Curtis and
Kim Curtis in Double Impact!
- I couldn't take a chance.
He's fool enough to!
- Don't be stupid.
I had no intentions of going
there and opening that gate.
- [Joel] Oh, now my
mouth's bleeding, Burt!
- Did you hear it, Doctor?
It sounded like a human voice.
I was thinking of Rook.
- But the livestock.
The shrews got into the barn!
- [Crow] The shoes
got into the barn?
- [Tom Servo] I better put
some alcohol on this wound.
(dramatic music)
- Let me guess, the
shoe's in the bar.
- What was it, Father?
- The livestock.
- [Joel] Live
socks, that's, huh?
- Mario, don't forget
to bar those doors.
* Booze glorious booze
- I put them in the barn myself.
- [Joel] What about
a bar mitzvah?
- They couldn't get
through the wood doors.
They dug through the dirt floor.
- [Thorne] Let me ask
you something, Doctor.
- [Tom Servo] Where
are the olives?
- How could you
expose all our lives,
yourself included, with
those things out there?
- [Crow] Did he just
become more southern?
- All you had to do
was get the Coast Guard
or the Navy to come in
here and burn 'em out.
- [Tom Servo] Give me that.
- [Thorne] Those
things got loose.
- Any unusual experiment
can produce unusual results.
- [Crow] Hey, that was my drink!
- That's why I
chose this island.
It's isolated.
Miles of open water
in any direction.
- [Joel] Miles of cliff
in every direction.
- Our project is
privately financed.
- [Tom Servo] Here comes
Art Buckwald again.
- Not a product for the
government or military.
And the world is in no danger.
- [Crow] Oh, I've been
going through the script
and I think I'm in this scene.
- This species does not swim.
- [Joel] Yes, fishes do swim.
- This island is their world.
- [Tom Servo] And welcome to it.
- Very soon, right
here on this island.
- [Crow] Appearing
will be Don Ball!
- Miniature reproduction
of an overpopulated world.
- [Joel] That'll
bring in the tourists.
- You will see the importance
of what we're working to avoid.
- I'm not concerned
about all this theory.
What I'm concerned
about is our lives!
- [Joel] And my Rob Roy.
- Yeah, well, time to panic
when they run out of food
and go on a 24-hour forage.
- How do you know
they haven't already?
- [Joel] Yes, say yes
to making Martini Rossi.
- That source could've
been depleted.
- [Joel] Well, we
need more brandy.
Need more scotch.
We're out of vanilla extract.
- There's still some
food on this island
before there's a crisis.
- Gin.
Michelob.
- Where?
- With his big mouth.
- [Joel] What?
It's paid for.
- Don't worry about
them digging in here.
The floors are tile.
- [Thorne] The walls
aren't, Doctor.
They're adobe.
- [Joel] Kill us!
- Our safest bet
would be on that boat.
- You may be right.
- [Tom Servo] I may be crazy.
- [Dr. Craigis] You can
reach your boat in daylight.
The shrews will
gorge themselves.
- [Crow] Booze is for healing.
- That should keep them
lethargic for several hours.
- There's no sense
looking at the dark side.
- And there's no sense
minimizing a serious situation.
It leaves you completely
unprepared to cope with it.
- [Crow] Hey!
- [Joel] Well you
took mine earlier.
- Now we certainly
can't make it tonight.
That's out of the question.
- Maybe tomorrow.
Someday, and soon!
- [Joel] Synchronized drinking!
- I have it.
We'll get some sleep tonight.
But we'll have a watch,
an hour and a half apiece.
Doctor, you go
first, then Radford.
- [Joel] I got mentioned.
- Jerry, and then me.
- [Joel] They're setting
up a Quarters game.
- Make sure they're
locked good and tight.
Check all these walls.
- [Crow] And roll
the brewmeister in
here so it's closer.
- Come now.
- No, I think I'll
stay here by the fire.
I'd feel safer.
- And closer to the bar.
- I couldn't stand it
in that room alone.
- All right, as you wish.
But try to get some sleep.
- [Tom Servo] But fart
and get some sleep?
- You know what I've been
thinking about, Mario?
- [Tom Servo] Socks,
I don't know why.
- Ann and that Captain.
- [Joel] Oh, the space
captain fantasy again.
- You and me.
- [Crow] We will need
a bigger room, then.
- Imagine an intelligent
girl like her
going for a common
sea tramp like him.
- [Tom Servo] Imagine in
how much detail, senor?
- I know why!
You do too.
- [Crow] Por que?
- In case anything goes wrong,
she's looking out
for her own hide.
- [Crow] 'Kay, it's typical.
- That's why I keep
thinking about you and me.
- [Joel] And Bobby McGee?
- Anything goes wrong?
- [Tom Servo] I'm not
Lisa, my name is Mario.
- We're gonna outlast 'em all.
(wind whooshing)
(thunder crashing)
- [Joel] Sinners repent!
- [Crow] Let's get
out of here, Scooby!
- [Joel] Shudder.
- I'm going to trust you.
- [Tom Servo] To tell
me when I've had enough.
- To take my turn in
patrolling the house.
(Joel hiccuping)
But when you're finished,
don't wake the Captain.
Come back here and get me.
- [Joel] Drunk.
- I'll probably feel good
enough by then to take his turn.
- [Tom Servo] He's having
his blood replaced.
- Okay, Mario?
- Si.
- Okay.
- [Joel] Don't touch me.
(wind whooshing)
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom Servo] Hmm,
let's see, I want bacon!
I want some bacon, yeah!
No bacon.
- No, he chewed up the slippers!
Bad shrew, bad shrew!
Little puppy?
(suspenseful music)
Puppy?
- Little puppy.
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] Ahh, those shrews know
they're supposed
to close the door!
- [Joel] Now, let's see.
I'd better finish up those pies
before the shrews get them.
Sure is taste-tempting,
all those yummy pies.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom Servo] Okay, right
over left, then left,
no, no, you've
got a granny knot!
(knocking)
- [Mario] Senor, it is Mario.
- [Crow] Oh, sir, pull
up the covers, please.
(Mario speaking
foreign language)
- A shrew in the cellar?
- Si, I hear him
singing down there.
- [Joel] He was singing?
- How did he get in?
- (speaking foreign
language) the kitchen window,
but I closed it off.
He went down there.
- Why should he go down there?
- The food for the little
(speaking foreign language).
(speaking foreign language)
- [Joel] What was
that about cojones?
- Did you tell Jerry?
- No, senor.
It is your turn next.
Here is (speaking
foreign language.
We kill him, no?
- [Crow] Oh, flashlight!
That's what he's trying to say!
- [Joel] It's Dave
Lennox and Dave Lennox
in The Lint Trap!
- [Tom Servo] Honey,
we're at Grandpa's, dear.
Wake up.
- [Joel] Man, I don't
mean to be rude,
but your eyes look like
two pee holes in the snow.
- [Crow] Soccer team!
- It's down in the cellar.
And we're going down after him.
But I don't want you to
let anybody open that door
'til I tell you to.
Understand?
- [Joel] Okay, anybody
can open the door
when you tell me.
Wait, wait, I
wasn't awake enough!
What did you say?
(suspenseful music)
Shrew, puppy?
I mean shrew!
- [Crow] Aw, this
is just like Aliens,
except without the underwear.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, I
like the underwear.
(suspenseful music)
- Okay, open it just a crack.
- [Crow] Okay.
- Open it.
- [Joel] How come
I have to open it?
- Hold on to it.
(speaking foreign language)
- Okay.
- [Tom Servo] Freeze!
(speaking foreign language)
- [Joel] Well, this is
just like that Happy Days
or Perfect Strangers or
Full House or Empty Nest
or Just the Ten of Us episode
when they get stuck
in the basement.
- [Crow] Gin, vermouth?
This is where they keep it all!
- [Tom Servo] Ooh,
we can burn all this.
Oh, no, there's a
Teddy Roosevelt costume
and some graves down here!
(Crow gasping)
(suspenseful music)
- [Joel] Ahh, there's a
Muppet behind the stairs!
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] It's all
right under the stairs.
- [Tom Servo] It's all right!
- [Joel] Honey, I think
we got puppets down here.
- [Crow] Hand puppets?
- [Joel] They're
under the stairs,
so I don't think
they're marionettes.
- [Tom Servo] Mr. Milkbones.
Rawhide chew toys.
- Mario?
- [Joel] Fine, thanks.
- Aqui.
I see where he was.
I do not see where he is.
- Cuidado.
- Si, senor.
I will be careful.
- [Joel] Car full?
- [Tom Servo] Oh, no, I
got shrew doo on my shoe!
(suspenseful music)
(growling)
- [Joel] Ooh!
- [Crow] Weasels
ripped my flesh!
- [Tom Servo] Bad
puppet, bad puppet!
- [Joel] Would've
got here sooner,
but it's a big basement.
- [Crow] Please don't ask
me to suck out the venom.
- [Tom Servo] I thought you
said your dog does Macbeth.
- [Crow] He's not my dog.
Well, it's the booze
brothers to the rescue.
- [Joel] Beware the dwarf!
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom Servo] What is it, boy?
(gunshot)
- [Crow] We will prevail!
Our state fair is
a great state fair!
Try the veal.
- You alright down there?
- Doctor, get down here quick!
- [Crow] I'm fine, but
Mario's not doing so hot.
- [Joel] Oh, bad idea.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom Servo] Hey, get off him!
- [Crow] No, he's got an
injury, see? (chuckling)
- Mario!
- [Tom Servo] Where'd
you hide the Cuervo?
- [Joel] Oh, he's got
rat scratch fever.
- [Tom Servo] Ooh!
(dramatic music)
Oh, well, look at the time.
I've gotta get to this
thing, I've gotta go.
- He's dead.
- [Tom Servo] He's red?
- [Crow] He's fed?
- [Joel] He's bed?
Oh, thank goodness!
- [Thorne] I got this
on him right away!
He couldn't have bled to death.
- [Tom Servo] Face
it, it's your fault.
- [Joel] Yep.
- Might as well let go of it.
Won't do him any good now.
- [Crow] Aw, get a body
bag out of the closet.
Can I have my gun back?
- What could've killed him?
- [Tom Servo] Oh, I don't
know, maybe that shrew?
- I'm not certain,
'til the autopsy.
- Hematoxic syndrome.
- [Tom Servo] Sounds
like a Ludlum book.
- I'm afraid so.
We'll know after pathology.
- [Crow] Scatology?
They study dung?
Ugh.
- That's not the same
animal you showed me.
That's a monster!
- [Joel] He grew up!
- They are mutants.
- [Crow] Ted mute-gents.
- In controlling
the size factor.
- [Joel] Ooh, that's a stretch.
- They seem to have crossed
some of the other
characteristics.
- Well, you certainly
did a good job of it.
- [Joel] Well, thank you.
- I've known that for
some time, Captain!
- [Crow] Ooh, I'm sorry.
I had that coming.
- [Joel] Now I'd like to say
a prayer, if nobody minds.
There, done.
- Mort!
- Would you please give me
a hand with Mario?
Radford, bring up the animal.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Tonight,
all dogs go to hell.
- [Tom Servo] Look,
he's levitating!
- [Crow] Next week
on Killer Shrews!
- [Tom Servo] Oh, turns
out it needs more vermouth.
Taste it, see what you think.
- Extremely high poison
content in the shrew's saliva.
- [Crow] But it's
smooth over ice.
- Now compare it with this.
Careful count isn't necessary.
Any indication the same
poison in Mario's blood
will give you the answer.
- Yes, you're right.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, I get it,
Mario's gonna become a shrew!
- Look, Ann.
- [Joel] You know,
you're really a drag
on these weekend getaways, dig?
- Brooding about it's
not gonna do any good.
- [Crow] But breeding will.
- Now why don't you try to
think of something else?
Tell me.
- [Joel] Do you collect
plates or anything?
- Are you a scientist?
- [Joel] No, I sweep
up, what do you think?
- Oh?
That's the study of
animal act, isn't it?
- [Tom Servo] Animal acts?
- What do you specialize?
What do you specialize in?
- [Crow] Oh, nothing special.
- Their diet.
I had a hand in this, too.
- [Joel] If I had a hammer?
(wind whooshing)
(creaking)
- [Crow] I like
you, you're nice.
You're pretty, but you're
just a summer thing.
- But this ends it.
If we ever get off this island,
I'll never have anything
to do with it again.
- What will you do?
- [Joel] I'm going to
eat a lot of bacon.
- Like normal women do.
- [Tom Servo] Storm
the beach at Normandy?
- Dull after the life
I've been living.
I'd rather dull and
alive than excited and--
- I'll take a dull,
alive woman every time.
- [Tom Servo] I
guess the other way
would be kind of
sick, wouldn't it?
(upbeat music)
- [Joel] Goll, is this
hallway ever long!
- [Crow] Just
strain and stir it.
- Say Thorne.
- [All] Thorne.
- The autopsy has proved
what we suspected.
- [Crow] He's dead.
He's dead as vaudeville.
- Several weeks ago I concocted
the most virulent poison I could
with the materials
I had at hand.
- [Joel] I had a free afternoon.
- To put about as bait.
But Mario was killed by poison.
- Doctor, I wonder
if you thought.
- [Joel] Nah, back off!
- The system of the
sorex allowed them
to assimilate that poison.
It remained in the salivary
gland of their jaws.
Isn't that wonderful?
- [Crow] Why, it's
better than Christmas!
- I am sorry.
Of course, I always speak from
the clinical point of view.
- [Joel] I didn't
mean to lash out.
- Something to
counteract that poison?
- Once Mario was bitten,
I'm afraid there wasn't
anything anyone could have done.
- [Joel] Bitten on the fredus?
- This indicates that
we cannot afford to get
even so much as a scratch
from these animals.
- [Tom Servo] Too pricey.
- They're more
poisonous than snakes.
- [Joel] Oh, I hate snakes.
- Best way to find out
is let 'em all bite you
and see which bites
you die after.
- We might just all
get that chance, Jerry,
you included!
- [Joel] Jerry Jerry fairy.
- I suggest we do the
same thing with this hall
and this lab and
cut down the chances
of getting in the
front of the house.
I think if we keep a close watch
on those walls and
windows in there,
we might make it 'til daybreak.
- The walls are two feet thick.
Do you think they have
a chance to dig in?
- Of course there's a chance!
- [Tom Servo] They have shovels.
- Anywhere that plaster's off,
that adobe's as soft as
mush where the rain hit it.
- [Crow] So do they
have any sort of closure
on this issue?
(suspenseful music)
- Hey, who's trilling?
Stop trilling out here!
Lionel, stop trilling!
Diana, stop trilling!
- [Joel] You know, the
big twist in this movie
is that the shrews are good
and they're just trying to do
an intervention on the humans.
- [Tom Servo] How deadly is
that doggy in the window?
(all humming Mission
Impossible theme)
- [Crow] Five minutes
to happy hour.
- [Joel] Those two are coloring
to pass the time over there.
- Here's another
possibility, Doctor.
- [Tom Servo] Gin omelets.
- It's very light out.
It's gonna be daylight soon.
- [Joel] And me wanna go home.
- We'll take the shrew
that killed Mario
and throw it over the
fence and use it for bait.
If they show up for it,
of course the run
for the boat's out,
but if they don't,
then I'll go down
and have Rook lay
to with the lighter.
Then I'll return to
the bend in the trail
and give you the
all-clear signal.
- [Crow] Could
you back up a bit?
The shrews in...
- Good, then you
explain it to the rest.
- [Crow] Yeah, sure.
Hey, you guys,
what's-his-name said something
about the thingamajig.
- [Tom Servo] Well, he's
chasing rabbits in heaven now.
- [Crow] Well, I
put the dog out.
I lobbed him over the
fence, and it wasn't easy.
- Well, the bait's been
out for 20 minutes.
Nothing's touched it.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Well, then I'm
going to change my clothes.
She is whisper thin.
- [Tom Servo And Crow] Mm-hmm.
- [Tom Servo] Starsky, wait!
(dramatic music)
Neat, huh?
Oh, wait, here's a
trick I taught 'em.
Stay, rot, good boy.
(laughing)
- [Joel] You know, we
really need to rake.
(gentle music)
* I am 16 going on 17
- Even the wind has gone down.
Isn't that wonderful?
- I'm afraid it's
not over, my dear.
- [Joel] The fingers snot over?
- Could be a lot more.
- He's right.
I'll be back at
the bend shortly.
Now you watch for my signal.
- You can't go now!
- I'll go with him.
- Not you, Father, you
haven't even fired a gun.
- [Tom Servo] He
doesn't love you.
- [Ann] Take Rad or Jerry.
- Sure, I'll go.
- [Crow] If I die, it'd
be a boon to the movie.
- And you'll be sure
of getting a signal.
- [Crow] I gotta go
make some raisin mash.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom Servo] Ooh,
shh, here he comes.
- [Joel] Oh, hi Jerry.
- [Tom Servo] Well,
coast is clear.
(all exclaiming)
- [Crow] Why don't they run
to the boat and drive away?
(dramatic music)
(Joel imitating music)
- [Joel] Music
sounds like Popeye.
Say, Jerry, I've been
meaning to ask you,
is that coat leather or vinyl?
- [Tom Servo]
Pleather, actually.
You're all gonna die
from shrew bites.
You're gonna bite
from shrew bites,
shrew bites, shrew bites.
- We've only got 20
rounds all together.
- I know that as well as you do.
- [Joel] Oh, we're in
agreement then, aren't we?
- Sherman, you
stay away from her.
- Do you have that
gun pointed at me?
- Right at the
middle of your back.
- [Joel] Well, that
is a part of me.
- We've got enough problems
without worrying about Ann.
- I'm telling you,
stay away from her,
or when the shrews
get through with you
they won't even
find the buckshot.
- [Crow] Ugh, ooh!
That must be how Festus
got his voice and his room.
- [Joel] Snag on him.
Snickers nag on him.
- [All] Eww.
- [Tom Servo] Heh-heh,
now I'm gonna send
some shrews over here.
Festus.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Hey, I thought the
shrews only came out at night!
- [Joel] Well, they
probably won't come up
if they're fighting and
all, they're carrying on.
(barking)
(all humming)
- [Tom Servo] I'm back
over here and I'm dead!
- [Crow] Don't do
that, they're dogs!
- Where's the skiff?
- [Joel] Have you forgiven me
for pointing that gun at you?
- I'll follow that check line.
I've gotta find him.
- Since last night you
won't find much of him.
- Would you shut up?
- I'm not going back.
- You what?
- I'm staying here.
- All right, you suit yourself,
but if I were you I'd
swim out to that boat.
- Shoot your self?
- Can't swim.
- Then stay here.
- [Joel] Can't stand.
- Wait a minute.
You've gotta give me a gun.
- [Crow] Are they doing
their vaudeville act again?
- A gun?
- [Jerry] Sherman, wait!
- [Tom Servo] Let's see,
where is that skiff?
I know it's around
here somewhere.
- [Crow] Ahh.
- [Joel] Hey, wait up!
Where do you think he is?
I mean, do you think he's dead?
How dead do you think he is?
I like your shoes, where
did you get your shoes?
Am I bothering you?
I'll try not to bother you,
I won't say anything ever again.
Oh, there I go again.
- [Crow] Well, either he's dead,
or they found Amelia
Earhart's stuff.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom Servo] Hmm, a
Dick Tracy campground.
- This is the gun
we had on the boat.
(suspenseful music)
They don't leave much, do they?
- [Tom Servo] I don't
know, they left a shoe,
a gun, a shirt, a belt.
Lots of stuff.
- Sherman, we've gotta
make a deal for us.
(shrews screeching)
- [Joel] Did I just step in
what I think I stepped in?
- [Tom Servo] Yep.
- They've been trailing
us on both sides.
- Where?
I didn't see anything.
- [Crow] They're starting
their routine again!
- You've gotta give me a gun!
(suspenseful music)
- [Joel] All right,
but don't kill me.
You promise?
- Whatever you
do, don't you run.
You stay in front of me,
'cause I don't trust you.
(suspenseful music)
- [Joel] Folks, see
what I gotta work with?
Buh-bye.
(Tom Servo humming)
- [Joel] You making
shrew noises back there?
- They're coming!
- To take me away, ha-ha!
- [Joel] Don't run.
Dogs can sense fear!
- [Jerry] Open the gate!
- [Tom Servo] Put down
your drinks and let me in!
- [Joel] He doesn't understand.
They're just as
frightened of you
as you are of them, okay?
- [Tom Servo] Speaking of
drinks, I've got an idea.
(whooshing
* That old black magic's got me
- Evening Mr. Servo.
Evening Mr. T. Robot.
What can I do for you tonight?
- Joel, buddy, it's
a code of the three.
No one in the place 'cept
you and me and Crow.
Anyhoo, me and my amigo
Crow here are gonna show you
how to mix a real drink.
- Yeah, jump back, Joel,
'cause this is not your average
pelican calypso flip or
hop, skip and go zombie.
- But it is one potent potable,
and it's our very
own Killer Shrew.
- Okay, here I go,
I'm at your service.
What do you want?
- Okay, listen up,
chocolate ice cream.
- Okay, chocolate ice cream.
- Captain Crunch
with Crunch Berries.
- Peanut M&Ms.
- Mrs. Butterworth's.
- Circus peanuts.
- All right, circus peanuts.
- Mr. Pibb.
- Marshmallow Peeps, lots
of Marshmallow Peeps.
- Okay, Marshmallow Peeps.
Isn't this gonna be kinda sweet?
- Just make the drink, barkeep.
SweetTarts!
- Vanilla frosting!
- Vanilla frosting,
got that over here.
- Wax lips.
- No, no, no, no wax lips.
You're thinking of
the Vulcan Mind Probe.
- All right, 86 the wax lips.
Now, music, maestro, please!
- All right, all
right, ready, okay.
(blender whirring)
- So, you live around here much?
- Have you seen that weather?
- Great hotel here, huh?
Been down to the pool?
- Aren't people here phony?
- All right, pour that into
the plastic tulip glass
and garnish with
a wind-up shrew.
- Hmm, you know what?
This looks pretty good.
You mind if I try it?
- Be my guest.
(thump)
(slurping)
- Whooo!
* Oh it is ladies' night
* Yeah the feeling's right
* Oh ladies' night
* Oh I want to
dance with somebody
* Whooo
- New rule, Frank,
don't ever touch me.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- [Tom Servo] Hmm, I'm fine.
- [Joel] Tasty.
(gunshot)
- [Joel] Here
comes the rat pack.
- [Tom Servo] Frank,
Sammy, Dean, Joey!
- [Crow] Joey?
- [Joel] Catch me!
- The shrews were out there.
I couldn't get the chance!
(all humming suspenseful music)
- [Joel] Never thought I'd be
so happy to see a fight scene.
- [Crow] Stick it to him.
I've got money on you!
- [Joel] Hey, it's
Laugh-In, look!
- [Crow] Swing and
a miss, wrong way.
(dramatic music)
(all imitating fight sounds)
- [Crow] That's illegal.
- For heaven's sakes,
Doctor, stop him!
- [Tom Servo] Doctor stop him?
(dramatic music)
- Do it, come on!
- You know you want to!
(all shouting)
(shrews chattering)
- [Joel] Aw, come
on, you big dummy,
all this stuff I gotta...
- [Tom Servo] I wish
I could do that.
(dramatic music)
(shrews screeching)
- [Joel] If you're not
going to buy a ticket,
you can't watch the game.
- [Crow] Well, I'll
mix up a pitcher.
- [Joel] You better.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Oh, well, I was
comforting her while you were,
huh-huh, gone.
- All right, didn't he have
it coming, or didn't he?
- [Tom Servo] That's your
conscience talking to you there.
- What happened out there?
- Oh, nothing much.
Jerry just tried
to kill me twice
in the last five minutes.
- [Joel] You know,
same old same old.
- [Tom Servo] Yep.
- Rook came ashore last night.
He's dead.
- [Crow] Or he's naked
somewhere, I don't know.
It's kinda leaning that way.
- This is all that's left.
Won't do us any good,
it's got no ammo.
- [Joel] Hey, lookie,
I found Kim Curtis,
TV's lovable Festus.
Can I keep him?
- [Crow] Just for that, you
can't drink for an hour.
- I'm deeply sorry, Captain.
- [Joel] Now Phillis George
is gonna make 'em hug.
- I wish I had
followed your orders.
- But Doctor, you casually
mentioned animals.
You didn't explain to us what
we were facing out there!
- [Tom Servo] Dogs with
weird stuff on 'em.
- You have every right
to feel the way you do.
My mistake was only
mine, one of judgment.
- [Crow] 20 lashes
with a wet noodle.
- I didn't know
about the hurricane.
I didn't anticipate the effect
it would have on the shrews.
- [Tom Servo] The
shwoo, the great shwoo?
- The house will be
safe for the crisis.
- How could you expose
your own daughter?
How could you
expose Ann to that?
- [Crow] She's adopted.
- She was going to
leave last week,
but the boat didn't come.
- I need a drink.
- [Joel] Aw, I wish you
would just get mad at me.
- Anybody else care for one?
- I could use some coffee.
- [Ann] I'll make some.
- Thank you, my dear.
- [Tom Servo] Good idea.
- Cream and sugar?
(shrew screeching)
(dramatic music)
- Oh, my leg!
- [Tom Servo] Stay, stay!
(gunshots)
You stay!
Stay, sit!
Good dog.
(gunshot)
Stay, good dog.
- [Joel] Well, I'm dead.
- You all right, Doctor?
- I just ripped my
trousers, that's all.
- [Joel] I'm fine, really.
- [Tom Servo] Uh-oh.
- [Crow] The end.
- [Joel] Yeah, enjoy
in moderation, my ass.
(dramatic music)
(gunshots)
- Oh!
- [Joel] Okay, you'd
better switch to coffee.
- [Tom Servo] The
money is in the, uh...
- There's still four
of 'em in there!
- [Joel] My hair, I
leave to Steve Allen.
My sport coat I leave to Bamuha.
- [Crow] Wow, he really
cruised those five stages.
- [Ann] Radford!
- [Crow] Look at him, he looks
weird without his glasses.
(dramatic music)
- He's dead.
- Now who'll pay
his part of the tab?
- [Tom Servo] Check his wallet.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] What's this say here?
Short little kraut?
Wait a minute,
conditions hellish?
What's going on here?
Mary Dawn Deardon.
- He recorded every
symptom and reaction,
right up to the
moment of his death.
- [Crow] But he's
a terrible speller.
Was with a Z.
- Jerry, tear down
one of those drapes
and cover him up.
- [Joel] Tear down a drink?
- Sure, I guess I'll cover him.
You'll cover me, but
who'll cover you?
- [Joel] Hey, is this one
of them funny joke riddles?
(blow landing)
- [Joel] She's my sister!
She's my daughter!
(blow landing)
- [Tom Servo] Well,
somebody's going to jail,
and it's not gonna be me!
- [Jerry] It'd take a tank
to get us out of here!
(suspenseful music)
- Look!
There!
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Hello, Doreen.
Hello, Shirley.
(shrew chittering)
- [Joel] Not the couch, I
just had it upholstered!
- [Tom Servo] That's nice, good.
Now the lamp, the
lamp would look nice.
Get the floor lamp and
bring it over here.
- It won't take them
long to dig around this.
- You're right.
Not telling where else
they're digging, too.
(dramatic music)
- Uh-oh.
- [Crow] Quick,
get another couch!
- [Joel] No, not the wet bar!
(mock sobbing)
(dramatic music)
- [Tom Servo] That'll hold 'em.
- Come on, the patio.
- [Tom Servo] Tooky-tooky.
- [Joel] We're
gonna barbecue now?
(Crow munching)
- Out here to
barricade those walls.
I'll tell you, we'll pile
some of those crates up
over there, and that
roof's our last chance.
- [Tom Servo] We're
gonna put on a show!
- Find something light!
(dramatic music)
(shrews chittering)
- [Joel] Hey, this is my beat!
- Here, help her
with that, Doctor!
Jerry, see if you
can find some rope.
- [Crow] Hey!
I found a wheat penny!
I'm keeping it.
- [Tom Servo] I found
some great stuff in here.
Check it out.
Golf clubs, and--
- Oh, he must be
the Dr. Smith of this movie.
- Doctor, we can use these
chemical drums as tanks.
Individual tanks!
- [Crow] Sort of like
a personal pan pizza!
- [Thorne] Set it down now.
- [Joel] Oh, it's
really cool in here.
Bang a hammer on it for me.
- [Joel] That, no, nothing,
nothing, wasn't doing anything.
Just standing around
back here. (whistling)
- It'll work!
It'll work!
- I'm too tall for the base.
If the shrews don't push
us over, the wind will.
- Not if we lash them together!
- [Joel] Well,
they're not really
personal tanks
anymore, are they?
- Only that one over there?
- [Tom Servo] Where?
Oh.
(men shouting)
- [Tom Servo] I'm gonna
put a wet bar in mine!
- Hey, know what?
I bet we could do
something with these wigs!
(clattering)
- [Joel] Yeah, help
out a little bit.
Hmm, bigger than the other one!
- [Crow] What a coinky-dink.
- [Tom Servo] What,
Shrew Be Gone?
We're saved, ha ha!
(shrews chittering)
- [Crow] What are they doing?
Oh, it's Flashdance.
He's an exotic dancer at night.
- [Joel] He's a maniac.
- [Crow] He's a maniac.
(upbeat music)
- Get some rope and
put it on that latch
so we can raise it
from the ground.
- [Joel] It's all
the same to Mary Lou,
calf riding, broody contests,
escaping killer shrews.
Yep.
- [Crow] Wait a minute,
they can chew through
adobe but not wood?
- [Tom Servo] Oh, hmm.
Poke him.
- [Joel] Hey, I changed my mind.
I think they're
gonna be submarines.
Watch that torch.
Two weeks later.
- [Tom Servo] Hi, have
a little fire, doggie!
- [Crow] Ooh, he bit my hinder!
- [Tom Servo] Ouch.
- [Joel] So what we're
doing here, Bob, is this.
- [Tom Servo] Four weeks later.
- [Joel] Does this plan
take more than a month?
- [Tom Servo] Hold it tight.
- [Joel] I call front seat.
(shrews chittering)
- [Crow] When bad dogs
happen to good people.
- [Joel] Little paws.
Cute little paws.
- All right, we're all set.
- [Joel] We are?
How can you tell?
- But we should be able
to just walk to the beach.
- [Joel] Oh, get Chuck Barry.
- [Jerry] There's a
lot of 'em out there.
I can see 'em on that door!
- [Thorne] Come down here!
That wind will blow you
right off that roof!
- I'm telling you,
I'm not going!
I'm staying here!
- [Tom Servo] Jerry, this
is Father O'Malley, boy.
Get down from there, will you?
- Jerry, Jerry, please
come down with us!
- No way, they'll get
you if you go out.
- Come down here, you fool!
- [Crow] Darn fool kid.
- I hope he makes it.
- [Tom Servo] Hey, we've
got some Cutty down here.
Nummy nummy, Jerry.
(Ann screaming)
- [Joel] A fiddler on
the roof, how fortunate.
- [Crow] Well, let's just hope
the dogs don't like sardines.
(whistling)
- [Joel] Oh, I've gotta
go to the bathroom!
- [Tom Servo] You should
have done that before.
(shrews chittering)
- [Tom Servo] Come
on, kiss your aunt.
- [Joel] Uh okay now
somebody's gotta get the door.
- Everybody ready?
I'm gonna open that gate.
- Now let's not walk in
four different directions.
- Ready?
- Ready.
- [Tom Servo] I guess.
- Okay here they come.
* Walking down the street
- Hold on, hold on!
- Hi.
(shrews chittering)
It'll never get off the ground.
- [Tom Servo] Regrets,
I've had a few.
I changed my mind.
- I'm feeling very
alone right now.
(screaming)
- Ann what's the matter?
- [Tom Servo] Oh nothing,
what do you think?
- You wanna rest, you tired?
- [Joel] Should we pull over?
(speaking foreign language)
- [Tom Servo] I can't
hear you, it sounds like
you're in a barrel.
- She said she's alright,
she's keeping her eyes closed.
- Alright, keep
your eyes closed.
- [Joel] Keep your
feet on the ground
and keep reaching for the stars.
- I'm still here.
- There's something wrong,
it's too heavy for her.
I can barely hold up my side.
- [Tom Servo] I'll say.
- I'll be alright in a minute.
- [Joel] You go on without me.
- Alright, you walk,
I'll drag for a while.
(dramatic music)
- Those dogs got
him under a barrel.
- Listen, don't let
their head get under.
They'll flip us over.
- Oops.
I'm yours.
(suspenseful music)
Nice huh.
Sure wish I had one of
them anti shrew barrels.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah I hope the
bar's still open down there.
- [Joel] Nice socks,
you know even as Festus
I admired his hosiery.
- Yeah it is nice hosiery.
- [Tom Servo] Oh I'll need
this, I better take this.
- A life preserver?
That might be kind of
ineffectual against
killer shrews.
- [Joel] Well it is a
life preserver you know.
(gun firing)
- [Tom] That stump has
been the cause of death
for a lot of people.
- It's Festus buffet!
He's really tasty!
That life preserver
adds texture.
- [Joel] Come on you guys.
- [Tom Servo] Meanwhile
on the Merrimack here.
Oops.
- It got my foot!
- Well give it to him!
- Now my foot is free
but it got my boot!
- Is there a scratch?
- [Tom Servo] Did
you save the receipt?
- No no mark.
- [Joel] Hey he's in a
portable confessional.
(gun fires)
Oh that hurt, oh.
- Keep moving.
Let's go, let's go!
- Full speed ahead!
- Okay I think this movie
just broke the goofy medium.
- I agree.
- Thorne, I don't think I...
- What?
- Now come on, the
movie would have ended
five minutes ago if it
weren't for your stupid boots.
- Dan, where's Dan?
- [Tom Servo] She gets this
way you'll have to excuse her.
- Thorne, we're close!
- We'll hit the water soon.
- Then we'll sink!
- Good, great.
Dive, dive, dive.
- Doesn't sound like they're
following us anymore.
- Oh my aching dogs!
- Woof.
- [Tom Servo] Oh yes, yes.
- We better walk deeper.
- [Crow] Deeper, deeper.
- I'm almost drowned out.
- Well can you swim for it?
- Okay.
(dramatic music)
(sighing)
- Oh no, piranhas!
- Sharks!
(light music)
- There we go.
- Well bad news folks.
Left the keys on the bar.
(speaking foreign language)
We are safe aren't we?
I mean the storm.
- Yeah me too.
- Sure.
Shrew got the first half alright
and that's always the roughest.
(kissing)
Anyway riding an anchor
I'll have a chance to
learn a little more
about that Swedish accent.
(laughing)
- In 24 hours there'll be
one shrew left on the island.
* To carry on, to carry on
An excellent example
of overpopulation.
- Well you know
something doctor?
- What's that?
- [Tom Servo] Your
daughter's hot.
- I'm not gonna worry about
overpopulation just yet.
(muttering)
(whooshing)
- Hey hold it you
guys, hey hey hey.
I know we wanted to do
a killer shrew sketch
sometime in this experiment
but these costumes
just aren't cutting it.
Oh ow ow!
That feels like when it's a
really nice Sunday afternoon
but you keep the shades
down in your home
watching the channel nine
movie and the announcer says
we will be back after Harry
and Walter go to New York.
(singing)
No, must read
letter before I go.
What the heck?
- Did I tell you my
saliva is poisonous?
- Put it up on (mumbles) Cambot.
I am 15 years old and a
huge fan of your incredibly
funny show though you may
not remember or perhaps
regret doing the Pants Up
Song is incredibly funny
and extremely clever along
with the Patrick Swayze
Christmas Carol and
Catalina Creeper Girls song.
You guys are very clever
and Mystery Science Theater
is the best show on cable.
I also present you with
my favorite show award.
Put that up on
(mumbles) Cambot please.
Letter.
You know only the support and
love of loyal MST3 viewers
can save us from killer
shrews and there why don't you
tell them the information
shrew Tom Servo?
(barking)
- [Tom Servo] Please for
the health and well being
of all of us on the
Satellite of Love
please send your information
and your letters to
Mystery Science Theater
3000 Information Club,
post office box 5325,
Hopkins, Minnesota, 55343.
(groaning)
- Oh my tummy hurts, I
had too much killer shrew.
- Oh there there Frankie, here
I fixed you something nice.
- Thanks what is it?
- An ipecac.
(spitting)
(light music)
- Burn 'em out?
Those things got loose.
- Any unusual experiment
can produce unusual results.